BIRMINGHAM. - DEMONSTRATION COMMITTEE. The members or this Committee are required to meet at the Association Room, Aston-street, on Tuesday evening next, on business of vital importance. -The meeting will commence at eight o clock.

Delegate Meeting. —A delegate meeting will be held at the Ship Inn, Steelhouse-lane, on Sunday next at two o’clock, when all places in the Birmingham district are requested to send a delegate.

LONDON. — Mr. Ruffy Ridley will lecture on Sunday evening next, at the Three Crowns, Richmond-sfcreet, Soho.

Mr. T. M. Wheeler will lecture at the Star Coffee House, Golden Lane, on Sunday evening next.

SHOREDITCH. — A lecture on Chartism will bo delivered at Albion Coffee House, 3, Church-street, Shoreditch, on Sunday (to-morrow) at eight o’clock in the evening; and a member’s meeting will be held at the same placo on Wednesday, March 2nd, at eight o’clock in the evening.

COLNE. — The Rev. W. V. Jackson, of Manchester, will deliver a lecture on Saturday (this day) in the Chartist lecture room, Windy Bank, at eight o’clock in the evening ; also, in the same place, on Sunday morning at half-past ten ; at Barnoldswick, at half-past two in the afternoon, and at six o’clock in the evening.

Mr. Edward’s Route for next week :— On Monday, the 28th inst. at Upper Warley ; Tuesday, the 1st of March, at Lower Warley; Wednesday, the 2nd of March, at Luddenden ; and on Thursday, the 3rd of March, at Midgley.

WALWORTH. — It is earnestly requested that the members of this locality would attend on Monday evening next, Feb. 28th, at the Ship and Blue Coat Boy. Walworth Road, as business of importance will be laid before them.

BRADFORD. — On Sunday next, Mr. Smyth will lecture at the North Tavern, at six o’clock.

WHITE ABBEY. — On Monday night next, at eight o’clock, Mr. Brook will lecture.

BRADFORD MOOR. — Mr. Arran will lecturo on Monday evening, at eight o’clock.

DUNKIRK STREET. — Messrs. Edwards and Ainley will lecture at Mrs. Shepherd’s, at eight o’clock, on Monday evening next.

LIDGET GREEN. — Mr. Ibbotson will lecture at this place, on Monday evening next, at eight o’clock.

Mr. Jones, the East and North Riding lecturer, will visit the following places during next work, viz : —On Monday, the 28th, at Hull; Tuesday, the 1st March, at Beverley; Wednesday, the 2nd, at Market Weighton ; Thursday, the 3rd, at Pockling-ton ; and on Friday, at York.

BEDLINGTON. — On Saturday evening. Mr. Charles Connor, of Manchester, will lecture to the inhabit aius of this place, and on Sunday, at Cram-lington.

Mr. Charles Connor's Route :—On Monday evening,at Sunderland ; Tuesday, at Durham; Wednesday, at Wingate Grange Colliery; Thursday, at Coxhoe ; Friday and Sunday, at West Auckland.

WILSDEN. — If the weather permit, Mr. Constantine, of Keighley, will preach here, in the open air, to-morrow noon.

MARYLEBONE. — Mr. Wm. Benbow will lecture at the Working Men’ Hall, 5, Circus street, New Town, on Sunday evening next. The chair to be taken at seven o’clock.

MIDDLETON. — Mr. James Leach, of Tib-streef, Manchester, wili deliver a lecture in the Chartists Chapel, on Tuesday next, Doors to be o pen at half-past seven o’clock, and the lecture to commence at eight.

Mr. O’Connor’s visit to Birmingham. — According to a letter addressed through Mr. White to the Chartists of Birmingham, Mr. O’Connor will visit this town on Wednesday, March 2nd, and continue here for three days.

STROUD. — A meeting of tho members of the Stroud Charter Association, will be held on Monday next, at seven o’clock, when business of great importance will be submitted to the members. It is wished that every member will attend.

WHITECHAPEL. — Mr. Ruffy Ridley will lecturo at the Earl Grey Castle, Luke-street, on Monday evening next.

TAILORS. — A meeting of the United Tailors’ bodies will be held at tho Social Institution, John street, Tottenham Court-road, on Monday evening next. Feargus 0’Connor, Dr. McDouall, and others will attend.

DEWSBURY DISTRICT. — A district meeting will be held here, in the large room, over the Co-operative Stores, on Sunday next, when every locality in the district is particularly requested to send a delegate, as business of great importance will be transacted. The meeting to commence at two o’clock in the afternoon precisely.

WIGAN. — Mr. James Dewhurst, from Bradford, will lecture in and around Wigan, for all the next fortnight, in order to agitate for the whole Charter and nothing less. All are alive in this quarter ; they are determined for the whole hog, bristles and all.

DEWSBURY. — On Sunday, February 27, Mr. H. Candy will deliver a discourse upon the frauds and impositions of priestcraft to commence at half-past six, at the large room, over the Co-operative Stores.

Mr. Candy will Lecture at the following places: — On Monday next, at the Association room, Barnsley ; Tuesday, at Staley Bridge ; Wednesday, Mottram ; Thursday, Hyde ; Friday, Stockport ; Saturday, Hazel Grove; Sunday, March 6th, Strand-street Association room, in the evening at half-past six ; Monday 7th, Oldham ; Tuesday 8th, Rochdale ; Wednesday 9th, Todmorden; Thursday 10th, Hebden Bridge ; Friday 11th, Mytholmroyd; Saturday 12th, Queen’s Head.

MACCLESFIELD. — Mr. West will lecture in the Association Rooms, on Sunday evening next, on the present position of the people and how to maintain it, as well as to shew up different parties who pretend to be friends, but who are in reality enemies.

SHAW, NEAR OLDHAM. — Mr. William Booth, of Newton Heath, will lecture here, on Sunday evening, at six o’clock in the evening.

BRADFORD, WILTS. — A county delegate meeting will bo held at Mr, Tucker’s, Westbury, on Sunday, 6th of March, when delegates from Bradford, Trowbridge, Meltsham, Holt, Frome, Warminster, Monkton Deverill, and other towns and villages will be expected, as business of great importance will be brought forward, at half-past ten o’clock.

ROTHERHITHE. — A public mooting of the working men of Rotherhithe will take place on Monday evening next, at eight o’clock, at the St. John’s Coffee House, New-street, Dockhead, for the purpose of forming a Rotherhithe Charter Association ; chair to be taken at eight o’clock by an old Chartist.

BRADFORD. — The Chartists of Bradford have engaged a room in Butterworth Buildings, opposite the Sun Inn, bottom of Ivegate. The Councillors and the lecturers meet, we understand, in the said room on Sunday next, Feb. 27tb, at two o’clock in the afternoon, to make final arrangements for the new plan. It is earnestly requested that every one will attend.

Mr. Dean Taylor’s Route for the ensuing Week. — On Sunday afternoon next, at two o’clock, if the weather permit, he will preach on Nottingham Forest; and in the eveuiug, at six o’clock, at the Democratic Chapel. On Monday evening, he will lecture at the Butcher’s Arms, Newcastle-street; on Tuesday, at Ilkestone ; Wednesday, at Sapleford ; and on Saturday night, at Carrington.

HEYWOOD. — A public ball will be held in the Hartley-street Association Room, Heywood, on Saturday, tho 5th of March. Tickets of admission, twopence, to be had at Mr. Thomas Wrigley’s, Chapel-street.

LAMBETH. — A lecture will be delivered on Tuesday, the 1st of March, at the Room, 1, China Walk.

SOUTHWARK. — Public meetings take place of the middle class of Southwark, every Thursday evening, at the Swan Inn, Dover Road, Borough, for the purpose of hearing the Chartists defend their glorious principles

Mr. Brophy will lecture at Entwistle, on Saturday (this day) at the Black Bull Inn, at seven o'clock ; and at the Chartist Meeting Room, Hollingworth, on Sunday, (to-morrow,) at half-past two o’clock in the afternoon.

BOLTON. — Mr. Griffin will lecture at Bolton on Sunday evening, and at Halshaw Moor, near Bolton, on Monday evening.

SHEFFIELD. — Mr. Woodcock will deliver a lecture to the Youth’s Association, in the room, Fig Tree-lane, on Sunday aftornoon, at two o’clock.
An address on “the duty of the people in the present crisis," will be delivered on Sunday everting, at half-past six o’clock, in the room, Fig Tree-Lane, Sheffield.

HALIFAX. — P. M. Brophy will deliver a lecture on Sunday next, at six o’clock in the evening, in the Association Room, at Swan Coppice.

A Public Meeting will be held at Westminster, on Friday next. Mr. O’Connor will attend, and address the meeting.

BRADFORD. — Mr. Brophy, from Dublin, will lecture at Bradford, on Wednesday evening next, at eight o’clock. The Council have succeeded in taking a room, in which to hold their meetings, situated in Butter-worth Buildings, Sun Buildings. The Council are requested to meet; next Sunday afternoon, at two o'clock, for the purpose of making a new plan for the lecturers.

