ROCHDALE. — Mr. Dunivan, of Manchester, will lecture here on Sunday next, at half-past two. Mr. Candy, of Wolverhampton, on Tuesday evening, at eight o'clock; and Mr. James Leach, of Manchester, on Thursday evening. The chair to be taken at eight o’clock precisely.

HEBDEN BRIDGE. — Mr. R. Wheelwright will address the female Chartists of Hebden Bridge, in the Association room, Hebden Bridge-lanes, on Wednesday, the 9th inst., at eight o’clock in the evening.

YORK. - TRIUMPHAL CAR LOTTERY. — In consequence of the continued applications for shares in the above lottery, and a few shares remaining yet unsold; the committee have determined, in order to allow their friends, desirous of purchasing shares, a full opportunity of doing so, to postpone the drawing of it to Tuesday, the 15th inst., on which day it will positively take place, and the results published in the Star.

MACCLESFIELD. — A meeting of delegates of the county ot Chester, will take place in the Chartist Association rooms, Watercotes, on Sunday, the 3rd of April, when all the delegates arc expected to bring forward their petition sheets, and likewise to establish a fund for a county lecturer; the Convention Fund must at the same time be transmitted to the general treasurer.

LEICESTER. - Mr. Cooper will preach in the Shakespearean rooms, to-morrow (Sunday) night, at hald-past six. Mr. Duffy  will lecture in the same rooms, on Monday night, at half-past seven.

CHORLTON-UPON-MEDLOCK. - A meeting will be held in the room, York-street, next Sunday afternoon, at half-past two, for the purpose of taking into consideration, the best means of supporting the victims to a cause, which has, at length, become dear to the hearts of nearly the whole of the industrious millions.

MR. THOS. BROWN SMITH will take an opportunity to address the Chartists of Hunslet on Tuesday evening, and will have much pleasure in meeting the friends at Holbeck on Wednesday evening next.—On the latter evening, Mrs. Smith will deliver a lecture on the signs of the times, and the duties devolving upon the people. All friends of freedom, especially professors of religion, are earnestly invited to attend.

BINGLEY. — A Delegate meeting wll be held in the Foresters Court, York-street, Bingley, on Sunday the 13th of March, at ten o’clock in the Forenoon, when all places within the district are requested to send a delegate, as a lecturer is engaged and will be in attendance ready to commence his route.

BRISTOL. — A lecture will be delivered in the room, No. 10, Nelson-street, on Sunday evening next, by. Mr. J. Forsbury, at half-past six o’clock.

THE New Female Association will hold their first meeting on Monday next, March 7th, at seven o’clock precisely, at the room, 10, Nelson-street. It is requested that females wishing to become members will do so as soon as convenient.

THE Masons' Committee sit every Wednesday and Saturday nights, from eight till ten, at the Castle and Ball, Lower Castle-street, to afford every one an opportunity of subscribing their mite, and to give any informatiom relative to the strike.

SHEFFIELD. — Mr. Richard Otley will lecture in the Political Institute next Sunday evening, at seven o’clock; subject, “as a nation becomes free the people becomes prosperous; as a nation becomes degenerated, the people becomes enslaved.” On Monday night, Mr. Wm. Gill will open a discussion on the present agitation for the Charter, shewing that the working classes, if united, can obtain the enactment of the People’s Charter as the law of the land in spite of the present opposition.

FIG-TREE LANE. — A lady will address the meeting on Monday evening next, at this place. Mr. John Marshall, the liberated victim of Whiggery, is expected to be present, to give an account of his sufferings.

FIG-TREE LANE. — A friend to the cause will deliver an address on Sunday evening, on the question of “Union with the middle class.”

SPECIAL MEETING. — A Special Meeting of the Members of the Association will be held on Tuesday evening. Every member is requested to attend.

MR. H. CANDY'S ROUTE for next week:-Monday, Oldham; Tuesday, Rochdale; Wednesday, Todmorden; Thursday, Hebden Bridge; Friday, Mythom-royd; Saturday, Queenshead; and on Sunday at Bingley.

TOWER HAMLETS. — A delegate meeting will take place next Sunday evening, at the Carpenter’s Arms, Brick-lane, at six o’clock.

A GENERAL MONTHLY MEETING of the members will be held at the Carpenter’s Arms next Tuesday, at which the usual balance sheet and some most important business will be brought forward.

Mr. M'GRATH will lecture next Sunday evening at seven o’clock, at the Rose, Twig Folly, Bethnal Green.

TWO OR THREE short addresses will be delivered next Sunday evening, by Messrs. John Prentice and Illingworth, at the Carpenter’s Arms, Brick-lane, commencing at eight o’clock.

Mr. PRESTON will lecture at the Buck’s Head inn, James-street, Bethnal Green, next Sunday evening at eight o’clock.

SHOEMAKERS, Star Coffee House, Golden Lane. Dr. McDouall will lecture here on Sunday next.

FAILSWORTH. — Mr. Rankin, of Salford, will lecture here on Sunday evening.

MANCHESTER. — On Sunday evening, Mr. Griffin will lecture in the Association-room, Redfern-street.

The Town Council have taken the Hall of Science, Camp-field, and placarded the town announcing that Feargus O’Connor, Esq., will deliver three lectures therein, on Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday, the 7th, 8th, and 9th of March.

STOCKPORT. — Mr. Candy, from Wolverhampton, will lecture here on Sunday next. On Thursday next, our chief, O’Connor, will be with us.

SALFORD. — On the 9th March, Mr. Jonathan Pickering will lecture to the Chartist youths.

DUKINFIELD. — Mr. George Johnson will deliver a lecture on Sunday evening, at six o’clock, in the National Charter Association room, Hall Green.

BINGLEY. — The Rev. W. V. Jackson will lecture in the Foresters’ Court, on Wednesday, the 9th inst. at eight o’clock in the evening.

SADDLEWORTH. — Mr. Pantrepact lectures at Delph this evening.

HOLLINGWOOD. — Mr. William Griffin will lecture here, on Sunday evening next, at six o’clock.

MR. DEAN TAYLOR'S route for the ensuing week:— On Sunday afternoon, at two o’clock, on Nottingham Forest, if the weather permit; evening, at Arnold, at six o’clock. Monday, at Calverton. Tuesday, at Hucknal Torkard. Wednesday, at Hyson Green. Saturday evening, at the Pheasant, Charlotte-street, Nottingham.

BERMONDSEY. — Mr. Benbow will lecture on Monday evening next, at half-past seven o’clock.

THE MEMBERS of the Dockhead Charter Association meet every Monday evening, at eight o’clock, at the St. John’s Coffee-house, New-street, Dockhead. It is expected no member will be absent on next Monday, as business of great importance will be transacted.

TEETOTAL meetings take place every Wednesday evening, at eight o’clock, at the Working Man's Chapel, Dockhead. The cause of temperance is going on gloriously in this locality.

THE members of the Bermondsey Provision Society meet every Monday evening, between the hours of eight and nine o’clock, at Sheirtcliff’s Coffee House, Abbey-street, Bermondsey-street. This useful society is doing good to the cause of the working class in this locality.

FINSBURY. — The Chartists of Finsbury are requested to attend at Lunt’s Coffee-house, on business of importance to the cause.

THE MEMBERS of the Finsbury Public Hall Committee, and all others favourable to the projected Hall, are requested to attend at Lunt’s Coffee House, on Tuesday evening next, when the Secretary will be prepared with the intended rules and regulations.

MARYLEBONE. — Next Sunday evening, Mr. John Watkins will lecture at 5, Circus-street, New Road, at half-past seven.

EAST END SHOEMAKERS. — This body intend having a ball, concert, and festival, for the benefit of the Convention Fund, at the Social Hall, John-street, Tottenham Court Road, on Monday, March 14th. Dr. McDouall will preside.

ST. PANCRAS. — Feathers, Warren-street, Mr. Frazier will lecture here on Sunday next.

HIT OR MISS, Globe Fields, Mr. Knight will lecture here on Sunday evening.

GOLD BEATER'S ARMS, Old St. Pancras Road, Mr. Spur will lecture here on Sunday next.

WESTMINSTER. — Ruffy Ridley will lecture on Sunday next, at the Charter Coffee House, Stretton Ground.

LEEDS. — Mr. John Smith will lecture in the Association room, Cheapside, to-morrow night, at half-past six o'clock, and Mr. G. S. Nussey will lecture in the same place on Monday evening at eight o’clock.

HOLBECK. — Mr. G. Hobson and another gentleman will lecture in the Association room, to-morrow night at half-past six o’ clock.

HUNSLET. — Messrs. Fraser and Stonehouse will lecture in the Association room, to-morrow night at half-past six o’clock.

HOLBECK. — Mr. Hill will lecture here on Tuesday evening next.

WORTLEY. — Messrs. Chambers and Longstaff will lecture here to-morrow night at half-past six o'clock.

WOODHOUSE. — Messrs. Chambers and Hobson will lecture at the Black Bull, on Tuesday evening at half-past seven o’clock.

CHURWELL. — Messrs. Fraser and Stonehouse will lecture in the Town’s-school, on Tuesday evening next, at half-past seven o’clock.

MORLEY. — Messrs. Longstaff, Hobson, and another gentlemen will address the men of Morley, in the Town's-school, on Friday evening next, at half-past seven o'clock.

ARMLEY. — Messrs. Fraser and Chambers will lecture at the Nelson's Arms, on Monday night, at half-past seven o’clock.

DEWSBURY. - A council meeting of the Dewsbury district, will be held at Birstal, on Sunday, March l3th, in the room over the Co-operative stores. Business of great importance is to be transacted.

NOTTINGHAM. - On Monday evening, a convivia meeting of Members of the various Operative Libraries, will be holden at the Rancliffe Arms, Sussex-street, Nottingham. The chair to be taken at nine o'clock.