OFFICIAL SUMMONS OF THE METROPOLITAN DELEGATES. The Members of the National Charter Association, of each locality in and around the metropolis, are requested to elect two delegates for the purpose ot transacting some very important business with the Executive Council, on Sunday the 10th of April, at two o’clock in the afternoon, in the meeting room, 55, Old Bailey. Delegates only admitted. P. M, M'Douall.

SUMMONS OF THE TRADES DELEGATES. The Delegates of the Trades National Charter Association are requested to meet the Executive, on Sunday, the 10th of April, at seven o’clock in the evening, in the Large Room, Craven Head, Drury-lane. P. M. McDouall.

BINGLEY. — The next delegate meeting will be held in the Foresters’ Court, Bingley, on Sunday, the 17th of April, at ten o'clock in the forenoon. Delegates are particularly requested from Shipley, Allerton, Clayton, Denholm, Conenley, and all other places within the district as business of importance is to be transacted.

HALIFAX. — Mr. Clark is expected to lecture here on Wednesday, the 13th, in the Association room, at Swan Coppice; the chair to be taken at half-past eight o’clock.

NEWTON HEATH. - Mr. William Rankin lectures in the adult's school room, to-morrow evening, at six o'clock.

HONLEY. — A district delegate meeting will be held at Honley, on Sunday, (to-morrow,) in the Association room; the chair to be taken at two o’clock in the afternoon, when delegates from the various localities are expected.

DEWSBURY. — A West riding delegate meeting will be held on Sunday, the 17th day of April, in the large room over the Co-operative stores, Dewsbury, on business of importance, relative to the People’s Convention, when all correspondence with the members will be laid before the delegates; all places are requested to send delegates. Chair to be taken at eleven o’clock in the forenoon.

DELPH, SADDLEWORTH. — Mr. Jones will deliver a lecture in the Mill Garth Lecture room, Delph, Saddleworth, on Saturday evening, April 16th. Subject—Are the labouring classes sufficiently intelligent to exercise the franchise with credit to themselves and advantage to the country at large?

LONDON. — Mr. Ruffy Ridley will lecture in the Albion, Church-street, Shoreditch, on Sunday, the lOth inst.

LIMEHOUSE. — Mr. Rouse will lecture on Wednesday next, at the Victoria, 3, Colt-street.

GOLD BEATERS' ARMS, OLD ST. PANCRAS-ROAD. — Mr. Anderson will lecture at the above place, on Sunday next.

CITY OF LONDON. — Mr. Wheeler will lecture at the Political institute, 55, Old Bailey, on Sunday next.

CAMBRIDGE ROAD. — Mr. M'Grath will deliver a lecture on Sunday evening, at the Queen’s Head, on the “Principles of the Peoples’ Charter.”

TURNHAM GREEN. — Mr. Wheeler addressed a few friends of the Charter, at the Bricklayers’ Arms, on Wednesday evening, when it was determined to join the National Charter Association, and several names were enrolled.

LECTURING COMMITTEE. - This body meets in future every Thursday evening at the Dispatch, Bride-lane, at eight o’clock precisely; all friends are requested to attend.

MR. MARTIN will lecture at the Three Crowns, Richmond-street, on Sunday (to-morrow) evening, next.

ARCHERY-ROOMS, BATH-PLACE, NEW-ROAD. - Mr. Duffield will lecture here on Sunday, the 10th of April.

CARPENTERS' ARMS, BRICK-LANE. — Mr. Rouse will lecture here on Sunday next.

MR. ROUSE will lecture on Tuesday evening next, at 55, Old Bailey.

CHELSEA. — Mr. Anderson will lecture on Monday, April 11th, at the Prince of Wales, Leader-Street.

HAMMERSMITH. — Mr. Duffield will lecture at the Black Bull Inn, Hammersmith-road, on Tuesday next.

BROMPTON. — Mr. Frazer will lecture at Thornton’s Coffee-house, on Tuesday next.

BUCK'S HEAD. — Mr. Southie will lecture to the weavers’ meeting here, on Sunday next.

MR. FARRER will lecture at the Shoemakers’ Clock House, Castle-street, Leicester-square, on Sunday next.

CAMBERWELL. — Mr. Anderson will lecture here on Wednesday evening next.

SHOEMAKERS. — Mr. Whitesides will address this body on Sunday evening next, at the Star Coffee-house, Golden-lane.

GLOBE FIELDS. — A public meeting will be held at the Hit or Miss, 79, West-street, Devonshire-street, Dog row, on Sunday evening next, at seven o’clock precisely, to elect a delegate to sit on the County Council, in the room of Mr. Thorn, resigned; when members are requested punctually to attend on business of the utmost importance to the association.

MRS. JOCELYN will deliver a lecture on Tuesday next, at 1, China-walk, Lambeth.

ROSE TWIG, FOLLY. — A lecture will be delivered here next Sunday evening.

TAILORS. — A meeting of this body will be held at the Red Lion, King-street, Golden Square, on Sunday (to-morrow), at eight o’clock precisely. All members are requested to attend, as business of importance will be brought forward.

ROTHERHITHE. - A discussion will be held at Bayley’s Coffee House, Church Passage, on Tuesday evening next, at eight o’clock. Subject—“Is the income tax a just tax?”

MR. WILLIAM JONES, the poet, will address the men of Rotherhithe, on Sunday evening next, at seven o’clock, at Bayley’s Temperance Coffee House, Church Passage, near Rotherhithe Church.

BERMONDSEY. — A Provision Society has been established in Bermondsey, and every information can be had at Mary Sherman’s Library, No. 2, Grange Terrace, Grange Road.

DOCKHEAD. - Business of the greatest importance will take place on Monday evening next, at the St. John’s Coffee House, New-street, by the members of the Dockhead Charter Association. It is expected no member will be absent.

BRADFORD. — A meeting will be held in the Chartist Room, Butterworth Buildings, on Sunday next, at six o’clock in the evening, when the delegates will give an account of the whole proceedings at Birmingham.

FARSLEY. — Messrs. Alderson and Rawnsley will lecture at this place on Monday evening next.

THORNTON. — Mr. John Arran will preach at the Chartist Room, on Sunday next.

LEICESTER. - Mr. Bairstow will preach a funeral sermon for Henry Frost, in the Shaksperian Room, to-morrow (Sunday) evening.

MR. JAMES LEACH, President of the Executive, will lecture in the Amphitheatre, on Monday evening next.

HALIFAX. — Mr. Clark, of Stockport, will lecture in the Chartist Association Room, on Wednesday evening next, April 13th. The lecture to commence at eight o’clock.

NOTTINGHAM. — A County Delegate Meeting will be held in the Democratic Chapel, Nottingham, on Sunday next, at ten o’clock in the forenoon, on business of importance.

MR. DEAN TAYLOR'S ROUTE FOR THE ENSUING WEEK. — On Sunday (to-morrow) afternoon, on Nottingham Forest, and in the evening, in the Democratic Chapel; on Monday, at Nottingham; on Tuesday, at Beeston; on Wednesday, at Ilkeston; and on Saturday, at Nottingham, at the Pheasant, Charlotte-street.

SALFORD. — Mr. Jones, from Liverpool, and the late West-Riding Lecturer, will deliver a lecture in the Town Hall, Salford, on Monday evening, when the Chartists of Salford and the surrounding districts are called on to attend. The chair to be taken at eight o’clock.

MR. CHARLES CONNOR will visit the following places next week:— On Monday, April 11th, at Northallerton; on Tuesday, the 12th, at Brompton; on Wednesday, the 18th, at Richmond; on Thursday, the 14th, at Darlington; on Friday, the 15th, at Barnard Castle; on Saturday, the 16th, at West Auckland; and on Sunday, the 17th, at Bishop Auckland. Mr. Connor intends to reside at Bishop Auckland.

HOWARTH. — On Sunday next Mr. H. Candy will deliver two lectures; one in the afternoon at two o’clock, "on the Evils of a State Religion;" the other in the evening, at six o’clock, subject, "Chartism in accordance with real Christianity.” Discussion invited.

MR. CANDY'S ROUTE:- Monday, April 11th, at Queenshead; Tuesday, Huddersfield; Wednesday, Mythomroyd; Thursday, Hebden Bridge; Friday, Todmorden; Saturday, Hazle Grove; Sunday, Macclesfield; Monday, Congleton.

ASHTON. — Mr. Clarkson will lecture in the Charter Association Room, next Sunday Evening, at six o’clock; subject, the evils in society and their remedy.

MR. WEST will lecture at Hull, on Monday; Howden, on Tuesday; and Leeds, on Wednesday next.

YORK. — The Chartists of York will have a ball in their Association Room, on Tuesday evening next, to commence at eight o’clock. Tickets 6d. each, to be had at Mr. Wilson Inglis’s, No. 4, Collier-gate, and at the Room, Ebor Tavern, Fossgate.

PORTSMOUTH. — The Chartists who reside in this locality are requested to meet on Monday evening next, at the Son of Freedom, Spring-street, Landport.

SUNDERLAND. — On Monday evening next, Messrs. Chapplin and Williams will hold a public meeting on the Town Moor, Sunderland.

ARNOLD, NOTTS. — Mr. J. Simmons, from Sutton-in-Ashfield, lectures in the Chartist Chapel to-morrow, afternoon and evening.

SOUTHAMPTON. — Mr. Ruffy Ridley will address the Chartists of this town on Monday, April 11th,

OLDHAM. — Mr. Jones, of Liverpool, will lecture in this town on Friday, the 15th instant.

DUKENFIELD. — Mr. Wilcox, from Ashton-under-Lyne, will deliver a lecture on Sunday evening, at half-past six o’clock, in the Room, Hall Green.

MARYLEBONE. — Mr. J. Savage will lecture at the Working Men’s Hall, 5, Circus-street, New-road, to-morrow (Sunday) evening, at half-past seven o’clock.

SHEFFIELD. - FIG-TREE-LANE. — Mr. Julian Harney will deliver a lecture on the war in Affghanistan, on Sunday evening, at half-past six o’clock.

A PUBLIC MEETING will be held on Monday evening, in the above room, Fig-tree-lane.

MR. J. W. SMYTH, of Bradford, will deliver a lecture in the large room over the Co-operative Store, Birstal, on Saturday (this evening), at half-past seven o’clock; and on Sunday, he will deliver a lecture at Dewsbury, over the Co-operative Stores, to commence at six o’clock in the evening.