Mr. PEPPER will preach at Sutton, at half-past ten next Sunday morning.

MIDDLETON. — Mr. Richard Littler, of Salford, will lecture in the Chartist Chapel, on Sunday, (to-morrow,) at six o’clock in the evening.

ON MONDAY EVENING, Mr. Breedon will address the Chartists of Loughborough at their room.

SOWERBY. - Two sermons will be preached in the Chartist Room, on Sunday (to-morrow,) the one in the morning, at half-past ten, by Mr. B. Rushton, of Ovenden, and the other in the afternoon, at three, by Mr. J. Shaw, of Huddersfield. Collections will be made after each sermon, to aid the Chartists of this place, in establishing a Sunday and week night school.

HEBDEN BRIDGE. — A public meeting will be held in the Chartist room, Bridge-lanes, on Monday next, at eight o’clock in the evening, for the purpose of confirming the election of delegates to the Petition Convention.

ECCLES. — Mr. Cooper, of Manchester, will lecture at Eccles on Monday evening.

LONDON. — Mr. William Benbow will lecture at the Working Men’s Hall, 5, Circus-street, New Road, Marylebone, on Sunday (to-morrow) night, at half- past seven o’clock.

ARCHERY ROOMS, BATH PLACE, NEW ROAD. — Mr. Wheeler will lecture here on Sunday (to-morrow) evening.

SHOEMAKERS, CLOCK HOUSE, CASTLE-STREET, LEICESTER SQUARE. — Dr. M'Douall will lecture here on Sunday evening next, at nine o’clock.

TEETOTALLERS. — Dr. M‘Douall will lecture at the Crown Coffee House, Beak-street, on Sunday evening next, at eight o’clock.

ALBION, SHOREDITCH. — Mr. Rouse will lecture here on Sunday next.

ROTHERHITHE. — Mr. Balls, of the Bermondsey Charter Association, will address the men of Rotherhithe, on Sunday evening next, at Bailey’s Temperance Coffee House, Church Passage, near Rotherhithe, at seven o’clock.

DOCKHEAD. — A Chartist Harmonic Meeting takes place every Saturday evening, at half-past eight o’clock, in the Dockhead Charter Association Room, St. John's Coffee House, New-street, for the benefit of the Convention Fund.

TOWER HAMLETS BOOT AND SHOEMAKERS. — A lecture will be delivered, on the principles of the People's Charter, at the Crown and Anchor Inn, Cheshire-street, Waterloo Town, on Sunday evening next.

WALWORTH. — A grand public festival, including tea, concert, and ball, will take place at the Montpelier Tavern, Walworth, on Monday, April 4th, 1812, the proceeds to be appropriated towards defraying the expences of the Grand Demonstration in presenting the Great National Petition to the House of Commons. Feargus O’Connor, Esq., is invited to preside. Double tickets, tea, concert, and ball, 2s. 6d. Single ditto, 1s. 6d. Double tickets, ball and concert. 1s. 6d. Single ditto 1s. Tickets to be had of the Committee, and at other places.

ST. PANCRAS. — Mr. Wheeler will lecture on Sunday (to-morrow) evening, at the Archery Rooms. Subject-“The superiority of the Chartist agitation over all others.”

TOWER HAMLETS. — On Sunday (to-morrow) evening at seven o’clock, an address will be delivered at the Carpenter’s Arms, Brick-lane, Tower Hamlets, on “Man, his relative, social, and political position.” The attendance of females is earnestly requested — mothers in particular.

MR. WEST, the East and North Riding lecturer, will visit the following places during the next week:- viz. Monday, at Malton; Tuesday, at Pickering; Wednesday, at Scarborough; Thursday, at Bridlington; Friday, at Holme; Saturday, at Beverley; Monday, the 11th, at Hull.

SHEFFIELD. — FIG TREE LANE. — Mr. Brophy, of Dublin, will lecture in the above room, on Sunday, Monday, and Tuesday evenings. Sunday evening, at half-past six o’clock. Monday and Tuesday, at eight o’clock. Full particulars announced by placard.

ROCHDALE. — Mr. Thomas Clark, of Stockport, will lecture in the Association Room, Yorkshire-street, on Sunday (to-morrow), at half-past two o’clock in the afternoon.

NEWSOME. — Mr. Edward Clayton will deliver a lecture on Monday evening next. Subject—“Class Legislation.” Chair to be taken at eight o’clock. Discussion invited.

DALTON. — On Wednesday evening next, a lecture will be delivered in the Association Room, Dalton, by Mr. Edward Clayton. Subject—“The rights and wrongs of labour.” The chair to be taken at eight o’clock. Discussion invited.

SOMERS TOWN. — Mr. Martin will lecture at the Gold Heaters’ Arms, Old St. Pancras Road, on Sunday evening.

WALWORTH. — Dr. M'Douall will lecture at the Ship and Blue Coat Boy, Walworth Road, on Monday, April 4th.

LIMEHOUSE. - A lecture will be given at the Victoria, 3, Colt Street, on Wednesday evening, April 6th.

HOLLINGWORTH. — An address will be delivered by one of the members of the Association, on Sunday next, at two o’clock in the afternoon, and every Sunday following, either by members of the Association or by lecturers.

OLDHAM. — Mr. James Leach, of Manchester, will deliver two lectures in the Town Hall, Oldham, on Monday and Tuesday next, the 4th and 5th of April. Subject —"The baneful effects of monopolies, and the most effectual means of destroying them.” The Lecturer will answer the charges brought against him by the anti-Monopoly Association, in a bill put forth by that party on Feb. 12th. Doors to be opened at half-past seven o’clock, and the lecture to commence at eight. Admission by ticket.

WATERHEAD. — Mr. James Duffy, of Oldham, will lecture here on Sunday next, at two o’clock in the afternoon, and at Oldham at six o’clock in the evening.

MR. JONES, of Liverpool, will visit the following places during the next fortnight:—Warrington, Thursday, April 7th; Eccles, Friday, the 8th; Chowbent, Sunday, the 10th; Salford, Monday, the 11th; Manchester, Tuesday, the 12th; Stalybridge, Wednesday, the 13th; Ashton-under-Lyne, Thursday, the 14th; Oldham, Friday, the 15th; Dobcross, Saturday, the 16th; and Rochdale, Sunday, the 17th.

MANSFIELD. — A delegate meeting will take place in the Association rooms, Watercots, on Sunday, (tomorrow,) when it is expected that a delegate from every Association in the county will be in attendance.

DUKINFIELD. — Mr. John Durham lectures tomorrow evening, in the room, Hall-green.

BURY. — Mr. John Murray, of Manchester, will lecture in the Jardin-street Lecture room, (late Working Man’s Hall,) at eight o’clock in the evening.

BIRMINGHAM. - A public meeting will he held at the Railway Station, Duddeston Row, on the 5th of April, for the purpose of affording the men of Birmingham an opportunity of again declaring their determination to stand fast by the whole Charter. Feargus O’Connor and J. B, O’Brien, Esquires, are expected to address the meeting.

HUNSLET. — Mr. T. B. Smith will address the men of Hunslet on Tuesday evening, at half-past seven o’clock, in the Temperance News Room, on the complete suffrage movement. Working men attend.