LONDON. - The Chartists meet at their room, Brown Bear, Southwark Bridge-road, on Monday morning, May 2nd, at half-past eight o’clock precisely, previous to joining in procession with the Trades, in Lincoln's-inn Fields.

SURREY AND KENT. — A GRAND DEMONSTRATION will take place on Monday next, to present the GREAT NATIONAL PETITION of the WORKING CLASSES. The Men of Surrey and Kent will assemble opposite St. John’s Church, Waterloo Road, at EIGHT o’clock in the MORNING, to go from thence in Procession to the central place of meeting, in Lincoln’s Inn Fields, to join the other Metropolitan Bodies.

WANDSWORTH. — A public meeting will be held at Mr. Fox’s, Frogmore, on Tuesday evening.

CITY OF LONDON. — A raffle will take place on Tuesday evening next, at nine o’clock, for a beautiful portrait of Feargus O’Connor, at Mr. Jeane’s, hairdresser, Snowfields, at 3d. per member, for the benefit of the Convention Fund. Tickets can be had of Mary Ann Sherman, No. 2, Grange Terrace, Grange Road; Mr. Ball, builder, 19, Edward-strect, Star Corner.

GUILD HALL. — A meeting will take place in a few days, at Guildhall, in the City of London, for the purpose of calling upon Lord John Russell to resign his seat in Parliament.

LONDON. — Mr. Mason will lecture to the Shoemakers, at the Clock House, Castle-street, Leicester-square, on Sunday evening.

CITY ROAD. — A Grand Gala and Ball will take place, at the Royal Albert Saloon, Shepherdess Walk, on Thursday, the 12th May next, for the benefit of Mr. Lunt, an old veteran in the cause of democracy and religious freedom. The entertainment will conclude with a splendid drama. Tickets, 6d.; reserved seats, 1s.; ball room, 1s.

LEICESTER SQUARE. — A Public Ball will take place on Whitsun Tuesday, at the Clock House, Castle-street. Single Tickets, 6d., Double ditto. 9d.

OLD STREET ROAD. — Mr. Edmund Stallwood will lecture to the Ladies’ Shoemakers, at the Cannon Coffee House, on Sunday next.

BATH PLACE. — Mr. Thomason will lecture at the Archery Rooms, on Sunday next.

DOCKHEAD. — A special meeting will be held at the St. John’s Coffee House, on Saturday evening, at half-past eight, on important business; every member is earnestly requested to attend.

MR. HARRISON, delegate to the Convention, will preach at ten o’clock in the forenoon, in London Fields, near the Cat and Mutton, and at three o’clock in the afternoon, in Weymouth Terrace, Hackney-road.

MARYLEBONE. — Mr. Bairstow will lecture at the Working Man’s Hall, No. 5, Circus-street, New Road, on Sunday (to-morrow). The chair to bo taken at seven o’clock precisely.

FOLEY-STREET, CLEVELAND-STREET. — Mr. White of Birmingham, will lecture to the Ladies’ Shoemakers, at the King and Queen, on Sunday evening next.

CAMBRIDGE ROAD. — Mr. Morgan Williams, delegate from Wales, will lecture at the Queen’s Head, on Sunday evening next.

NEW ROAD. — A Member of tho National Convention of the Industrious Classes, will deliver a lecture at the Archery Rooms, Bath Place, on Sunday evening next, to commence at half past seven o’clock. The members are particularly requested to attend.

WALWORTH. — The members meet at eight o’clock, on Sunday (to-morrow) evening, and it is earnestly hoped that the whole of the members will be present. All members holding petition sheets will bring them in on Sunday evening, or before, to the secretary, W. Pedley, No. 5, Southampton-sireet, Camberwell.

TOWER HAMLETS. — The friends are requested to attend a special general meeting, at the Carpenter’s Arms, Brick-lane, on Sunday evening next, at six o’clock precisely, to take in hand some of the most important business in the forthcoming demonstration.

BATH. — Mr. Bartlett lectures to-morrow evening.

BRISTOL. — The friends of Chartism in Bristol are respectfully informed that Bear Lane Chapel, Temple-street, is open every Sunday morning, from the hours of ten till one, for reading and mutual instruction; on Wednesday evenings, at eight o’clock, for discussions and lectures; and on Monday evenings, at the same hour, for the enrolment of members, and the general business of the Association.

NOTTINGHAM. — Mr. Lowe, from Bagthorpe, will preach in the Democratic Chapel, on Sunday afternoon and evening.

NEWARK. — A Chartist tea party and ball is to be held on Whit-Monday. Tickets, nine-pence each, to be had of Messrs, Simnitt and Saunders.

NOTTINGHAM. — Mr. Taylor will lecture at the George on Horseback, on Monday evening next; at Old Basford, on Wednesday evening; and on Saturday evening, at the Noah’s Ark, Coalpit-lane.

SUTTON-IN-ASHFIELD. — A delegate meeting will be held in the Chartist Reading Room, on Sunday (to-morrow), at two o’clock in the afternoon, to take into consideration the forthcoming demonstration, and to elect a delegate to attend the delegate meeting at Nottingham, which is to be held on the 8th of May.

A PUBLIC MEETING of the female Chartists of Sutton-in-Ashfield, will be held in the Chartist Reading Room, at three o’clock, on Monday, May 2nd.

MANCHESTER. — A lecture will be delivered in the Hall of Science, by Mr. Watts, on Tuesday, the 3rd of May, in behalf of the sufferers, and the damage done to the hall by the late outrage. It is expected that the friends of liberty will attend.

MACCLESFIELD. — A county delegate meeting will take place on Sunday forenoon, at eleven o’clock, in the Chartist Association Rooms, Watercotes, when delegates from every Association in the County are requested to attend, and to bring or forward their quota of the Convention and lecturers’ fund.

STOCKPORT. — Mr. Henry Smethurst, of Oldham, will lecture here to-morrow evening, at six o’clock.

ROCHDALE. — Mr. Dunivan, of Manchester, will lecture here next Sunday (to-morrow,) at half-past two in the afternoon, and six in the evening, in the Association Room, Yorkshire-street.

BURY. — Mr. JOSEPH LINNEY, of Manchester, will lecture here on Monday next, in the Garden-street Lecture Room, at eight o’clock in the evening.

HALIFAX. - A Chartist room will be opened on Saturday, the 30th, (this day,) at seven o’clock in the evening, at Mr. Henry Wormersley’s Temperance Hotel, in Copper-street, near Hall End.

HONLEY. - A District Delegate Meeting will be held this day, (Saturday,) at six o’clock, in the Association Room, Honley, when delegates from every quarter of the district are expected.

THE EAST AND NORTH RIDING DELEGATE MEETING will be held at the Temperance Hotel, Selby, on Sunday (to-morrow,) at half-past ten o’clock in the forenoon.

P. M. BROPHY'S ROUTE for the ensuing week. - At Longton, in the Potteries, on Monday, May 2nd.; Stoke, the 3rd; Hanley, the 4th; Burselm, the 5th; Tunstal, the 6th; and at Macclesfield, on Sunday, the 8th.

MR. BROPHY has made arrangements to be at Arnold, Basford, Calverton, Sutton-in-Ashfield, and Newark, during Whitsun week.

HEYWOOD. — Mr. Isaac Burrow, of Bolton, will deliver two lectures here, on Sunday, the 8th of May, and not on the 1st, as previously announced.

BACUP. — There will be held a public meeting on Sunday, the 1st of May, on Derply Common, when Mr. Tattersall, of Burnley, will address the meeting, and several other speakers from the surrounding districts are expected to be present.

ASHTON. — Mr. James Cartledge, of Manchester, will lecture in the Chartist Association Room, on Sunday (to-morrow), at six o’clock in the evening.

BINGLEY. — A delegate meeting will be held in the Foresters’ Court, York-street, Bingley, on Sunday, the 8th of May, at ten o’clock in the forenoon.

MIDDLETON. — Mr. John Leach, of Rochdale, will lecture here next Sunday (to-morrow) at six o’clock in the evening.

HEBDEN BRIDGE. - A public meeting will be holden at Mount-Skip, in Wadsworth, on Monday next, at three o’clock in the afternoon, in honour of the National Petition being presented. Mr. Bell is expected to address the meeting. The various associations will meet at twelve o’clock at Hebden Bridge, and march in procession through Mytholmroyd and Midgley, to the place of meeting.

ROTHERHAM. — Mr. T. B. Smith will lecture on Wednesday evening, on the benefits of knowledge and the progress of society.

SHEFFIELD. - FIG-TREE-LANE. — Mr. Harney will address the Sheffield Chartists, on the alarming state of the country and the duty of the people, on Sunday evening, at seven o’clock.

MR. PARKES will deliver a lecture, (at the request of the Female Association) on the rights and duties of women, in the above room, on Monday evening, at half past seven o’clock. The attendance of our brother democrats is respectfully invited.

SOWERBY. — On Sunday next, Mr. Bell will lecture in the Chartist Room, at half-past two o'clock in the afternoon.

HOLLINWOOD. — Mr. John Bailey, of Manchester, lectures here on Sunday evening next, at six o’clock.

BRADFORD. — A lecture will be delivered at the Masons’ Arms, Club Houses, this evening, on behalf of the Association.

COUNCIL ROOM. — Messrs. Jennings and Carodus wil lecture here, on Sunday evening, at six o’clock.

FOUR-LANE ENDS. — Messrs. Smyth and Kell will lecture here, on Monday evening next, at eight.

GOLDEN COCK. — Mr. Smyth will lecture on the repeal of the Union, on Sunday evening, at seven o’clock.

ECCLESHILL. — Mr. Dewhirst will lecture on Eccleshill Moor, in the open air, at two o’clock, on Sunday afternoon next.

DEWSBURY. — Mr. West will preach two funeral sermons for Henry Frost, on Sunday next, in the Large Room over the Co-operative Stores, when collections will be made for the benefit of Mrs. Frost. Service to commence at half-past two, and half-past six.

DEWSBURY DISTRICT. — A Council Meeting will be held at Birstal, on Sunday, May 8th, in the Association room, over the Co-operative Stores, to commence precisely at two o’clock in the afternoon, when delegates from all parts of the district are requested to attend.

CLECKHEATON. — Mr. T. B. Smith will preach two sermons at this place, on Sunday, May 8th, service to commence in the morning at ten o’clock, and in the evening at six. Should the weather be favourable, Mr. T. B. Smith will preach at Little Town in the afternoon, at two o’clock, in the open air.

BARNSLEY. — Mr. T. B. Smith will deliver three lectures at Barnsley, on the evenings of Saturday, Sunday (in connection with divine service), and Monday, the 30th of April, and the 1st and 2nd of May, in the Odd Fellows’ School Room. Lecture first—“On anti-tobaccoism and teetotalism.” Lecture second—“On the necessity of establishing Sunday Schools, in which the children of the working classes may receive a good moral and secular education.” Lecture third—"On the great principles of Chartism.” Mr. Smith will attend and preach at the Chartist Camp Meeting, on Barebones, on Sunday afternoon.

MEETING. — There will be a meeting of the Council held in the Association Room, on Sunday, at four o’clock in the afternoon, on business of great importance; also a meeting at seven o’clock on Monday evening, in the same place.

MR. JONES will visit the following places during the next week Hebden Bridge, Monday, May 2d; Halifax, on Tuesday; Huddersfield, Wednesday; Barnsley, Thursday; Doncaster, Friday; Rotherham, Saturday.

FAILSWORTH. — Mr. William Booth will lecture on Sunday evening next, at six o’clock.

NEWTON HEATH. — Mr. Massey will lecture on Sunday evening next, at six o'clock.

CRAGGVALE. — Mr. Bell will lecture on Monday, May 2nd.

BIRMINGHAM. — The Council in Aston-street will meet on Thursday night, at half-past seven o’clock.

STEELHOUSE-LANE. — The members of the Association meeting at the Ship, are earnestly requested to assemble on Tuesday evening next.

PUBLIC DINNER. — It is contemplated to get up a public dinner to Feargus O’Conner, Esq.; at which an address will be presented to that gentleman from the Chartists of Birmingham.

DUKENFIELD. — The Chartists meet in their room, Hall Green, to-morrow evening, at six o’clock.

LEEDS DISTRICT. — The committee for establishing associations in the surrounding villages is requested to meet on Tuesday night in the Holbeck Association Room, at half-past seven o’clock.

CRAIG BOTTOMS. — Mr. William Bell, of Heywood, will lecture here on Monday evening.

MOSSLEY. — Mr. Griffin, of Manchester, lectures here this evening.

MR. WEST'S ROUTE for the ensuing week:—Overton, Monday, May 2nd; Adwalton, Tuesday; Wednesday, at Great Gomersall; Thursday, at Potovens; Friday, at Batley; Saturday, at Dawgreen.