COALBROOK DALE. - CHARTIST DEMONSTRATION. - On Whitsun Tuesday, the 17th instant, the members and friends of the Coalbrook Dale Association intend to hold a Chartist demonstration on the Wrekin, and respectfully, yet urgently, invite the co-operation of all the Chartists in Shropshire, or the surrounding counties, they having adopted the old Tory toast of "all friends round the Wrekin.” It is the intention of the Dale Chartists to meet their Salopian and other friends in Watling-street, near Wellington, at 11 o’clock, and from thence proceed, with banners and music, to the Wrekin. Mr. Mason and several other gentlemen are expected.

DUDLEY. — Mr. Candy will lecture here on Whitsun Wednesday.

BILSTON. — A grand ball will be held in the large association room, Stafford-street, on Whit Monday; musicians are already engaged for the purpose; tickets fourpence each, to be had at the following places:— namely, at Mr. Thomas Rogers, Walsall-street; Mr. Robert Gettings, Oxford-street; Mr. John Jones, hair-dresser, Wolverhampton-street; and at the Co-operative Stores, Stafford-street.

DARLASTON. — A delegate meeting of great importance, will be held at the Seven Stars Inn, Darlaston, at two o'clock on Whit-Sunday, May 15th, when delegates from the following places, are earnestly requested to attend:—Dudley, Wednesbury, Walsall, Wolverhampton, and Bilston, when business respecting the district lecturer will be transacted, and other matters of importance.

DERBY. — The Chartists of this town, will have a tea party and ball at Mr. Pegg’s, Tanner’s Arms, on Tuesday in Whitsun week.

HOOLEY HILL. — On Monday, May 16th, Mr. Dixon, of Wigan, will deliver a lecture at this place, at seven o’clock in the evening.

NOTTINGHAM. — A County delegate meeting will be held at the Democratic Chapel, Rice Place, on Sunday next, when it is requested that all places in the locality will send delegates, as business of importance will be brought forward.

MR. SIMMONS, from Sutton, will preach two sermons on the Forest, on Sunday, May 8th, at two in the afternoon, and six in the evening.

MR. COOPER, from Leicester, will preach two sermons on the Forest, on Whit-Sunday afternoon and evening.

BRADFORD. — A lecture will be delivered at the Masons' Arms, Church Houses, on Saturday (this evening) by Mr. Edwards, on behalf of the Association.

RAMSBOTTOM. — Mr. James Duffy will open an Association at Mr. James Taylor’s, the Dun Horse Inn, on Monday, May the 9th, at eight o’clock in the evening.

LITTLE HORTON. — Mr. J. Arran will lecture in the Chartists' Room, on Sunday evening next, at six o’clock.

ADWALTON. — A Chartist Camp Meeting will be held at this place to-morrow, at two o’clock in the afternoon.

LONG LAND'S PLACE. — Messrs. Alderson and Rawnsley will lecture on Wednesday evening next.

ARNOLD. — Mr. Soar, from Nottingham, will preach in our Chapel on Sunday evening next, at six o'clock.

CHOWBENT. — Mr. Isaac Barrow, of Bolton, will deliver two lectures in Harrison’s Chapel, on the 15th instant. The lectures to commence at half-past two o’clock in the afternoon, and at half-past six in the evening. Collections will be made at the close of each lecture, to defray the expences of the Chapel.

MIDDLETON. — Mr. Wilson will deliver a lecture in the Chartist Chapel, on Monday next, “On the present alarming state of the country, the cause of it, and its remedy.” Doors to be opened at half-past seven o’clock, and the lecture to commence at eight.