BURY. — The Rev. W. V. Jackson will address the people of Bury, in the Garden-street Leoture Room, on Monday, December 13th, at eight o’clock in the evening.

MILNROW. — Mr. James Cartledge lectures here on Sunday evening, tho 12th instant, at six o’clock.

UPPER WORTLEY. — Mr. Parker, of Leeds is expected to preach on Sunday, (to-morrow,) afternoon and evening. On Monday evening a public meeting of the inhabitants will be held in the Chartist Room, to take into consideration the noble conduct of the masons who have recently struck against their foreman, Allen, at the.new Houses of Parliament. Important details will be laid before the meeting.

MARYLEBONE. — A special meeting is to be holden to-morrow morning at ten o’clock, Mr, Watkins lectures in the evening at half past seven.

Mr. Mason’s Route for this week - Darleston, on Monday ; Walsall, on Tuesday ; Wolverhampton, on Wednesday ; Bilston and adjacent villages, on Thursday, Friday, and Saturday.

HUNSLET. — Mr. T. B. Smith will preach on Sunday evening, at six o’clook. On Tuesday evening a public meeting will be held on behalf of the masons now on strike in London, when most important information will be detailed to the meeting.

HYDE. — Mr. Charles Davis, of Stockport, will deliver a leoture in the Working mans’ Institution, Hyde, on Monday, the 6th inst., at half-past seven o’clock at night.

SOUTHWARK. — A public meeting, convened by the High Bailiff, will be held at the Town Hall on Monday, at half-past twelve o’clock, to petition Parliament, and address her Majesty on the present distressed state of the country. Men of Southwark, attend ! The meeting is your own, and the National Petition will be adopted.

LAMBETH. — A public meeting will be held at the Horn’s Tavern, at Kennington, to address her Majesty, on Tuesday evening, at seven o’clock precisely.

The meeting at the Chartist Hall, 1, China Walk, will not be held until the close of the meeting at the Homs, in consequence of the members wishing to evince their loyalty to her Majesty in a straightforward manner.

STROUD. — The Chartists of Stroud, are, requested to be early in their attendance at their room on Monday, Dec. 6th, as business of importance will be submitted.

LONDON. — Dr. M‘DoualI lectures to-morrow, at the Knave of Clubs, Club Row, Church-street, Bethnal Green, at half-past seven o’clock in the evening. Mr. Lee lectures to-morrow at the Charter Coffee House, Stretton Ground, Westminster.

LEEDS. — Mr. Stallwood lectures this evening on anti-Corn Law fallacies. He lectures also to-morrow afternoon and night.	

Mr. Stallwood. Mr. Stallwood’s present successful tour will terminate at Leeds on Sunday next, December 5th, when he will be open to engagements. Mr. Stallwood would be happy to lecture in any of the large towns, en route to London. Communications addressed to him, post-paid, on or before Monday next, at the Star office, will be attended to.	

NEWTON HEATH. — There will be a discussion in the adult school this evening, the 4th of December. Subject—“ Whether will it be better to, pursue the plan of Feargus O’Connor, of getting upon the land, or a repeal of the Corn Law !” . All who are in favour of free discussion are desired to attend. On Monday next, Dec. 6th, Mr. Joseph Linney will lecture in the above place, at eight o’clock in the evening. On the 13th instant there will be a lecture delivered by a friend.

BERMONDSEY. — Mr. Balls will lecture here Tuesday next.

TOWER HAMLETS. — Mr. Farrer will lecture at the Carpenter’s Arms, Brick Lane, on Sunday, Dec. 5th.

FINSBURY. — Mr. Wheeler will lecture here on Monday, Dec. 4th.

HANLEY. — Mr. Robson and Mr. M’Grath will lecture at Weston’s Temperance Hotel, on Tuesday next.

LIMEHOUSE. — Mr. Martin will leoture at the Association-room, Limehouse Causeway, on Tuesday next.	

TAILORS, RED LION, KING STREET, GOLDEN SQUARE. — Mr. Wheeler will address them on Sunday next.

Lunt’s Coffee Room, Finsbury. — Mr. Farrar will lecture here on Tuesday, Dec. 7th.

CHATHAM. — Dr. McDouall will lecture to the friends at this place on Thursday and Friday next.

HOLLINGWORTH. — Mr. Doyle lectures here to-morrow afternoon.

ROCHDALE. — Mr. Clarke lectures here to-morrow.

DARLINGTON. — Mr. Mann, from Middlesbro*, will lecture in Mr. Bragg’s large room, Priest-gate, on Monday evening, at eight o’clock.

NOTTINGHAM. — Mr. G. Harrison will preach in the Democratic Chapel, Nottingham, on Sunday next.

Mr. Dean Taylor will visit the following places, next week: Calverton, Sunday ; Nottingham, Monday ; Arnold, Tuesday ; Lambley, Wednesday; Ruddington, Thursday.

EAST AND NORTH RIDING DISTRICT. — Mr, Jones, the East and North Riding Lecturer, will visit the following places during the ensuing month, viz,:— Monday, the 6th and 20th at Hull; 7th and 21st, at Beverley; 8th, 22nd, and 30th, at Market Weighton; 9th and 23d, at Holme ; 10th and 29th, at Bridlington ; 11th and 28th, at Scarborough; 13th and 27th, at Malton ; 14th and 25th, at York; 15th and 24th, at Pooklingion ; 16 th and 31st, at Howden ; 17th Dec. and 1st January, at Selby ; 18th, 19th Dec. and 2nd Jan. at Leeds ; 3rd and 4th January, at Knaresborough.

MILNROW. — A public meeting will he held in the Chartist Room, on Monday evening next, to take into consideration the propriety of adopting the petition of the industrious classes. Chair to be taken at eight o’clook. Mr. James Greaves, from Shaw, and other friends from Rochdale, have been invited to address the meeting,

Mr. Doyle’s Route for the ensuing week, will be : - Mottram on Sunday, 5th December ; Hazle-grove, 6th ; Macclesfield, 7th ; Congleton, Wednesday, 8th; Middlewich, Thursday, 9th; North-wiob, Friday, the 10th.

MACCLESFIELD. — A county delegate meeting will assemble in the Chartist Association Rooms, Water-cotes, Macclesfield, on Sunday, the, 12th of December, when business of the utmost importance will be laid before them; and it is requisite that each delegate do bring his quota for the payment of the lecturer, and the state of the Association he comes from.

SOUTHWARK. — Men of the borough of Southwark, attend to your duty by attending at the Town Hall, on Monday next, Dec. 6th, at half-past twelve o’clock precisely, to adopt the National Petition, and also to address her Majesty upon the present unparalleled distressed state of the country, and show to your opponents that your cause is just. A great victory has been gained, therefore rally round your standard. Universal Suffrage and no surrender !

STANNINGLEY. — Mr. Arran will lecture at Stanningley, on Sunday (to-morrow) in the afternoon at two o’clock,

OLDHAM. — Mr. Henry Smethurst will lecture on Sunday, Dee. 5th, in Greaves-street, at six o'clock in the evening.

BARNSLEY. — The demonstration committee meet this evening, at Mr. Hoey’s, to make further arrangements for the reoeption of Mr. O’Connor.

SALFORD. — On Sunday night next, Mr. William Booth, from Newton-heath, will lecture in our association room. Great George-street, at half-past six o’clock in the evening. Mr. O’Brien will lecture in the large room of the Salford Town-hall, on Monday next, December 6th, at eight o’clock in the evening.

SHEFFIELD. — The members of the general council will meet on Sunday, December the 5th, at two o’clock.
	Sunday Eve Lecture.— A political lecture will be delivered on Sunday evening, December the 5th, at half-past six o'clock, in the room, Fig-Tree-Lane.

National Charter Association. — The usual public meetings will be held on Monday, December the 6th ; on Tuesday, the 7th, the members of the association will meet. Important business will be brought before them.

THE LONDON MASONS. — A general meeting of delegates from the trades of Sheffield, will be held at the Grey Horse, High-street,on Monday evening; December the 6th, at seven o’clock, to take into consideration the case of the masons, lately employed at the new Houses of Parliament, now on strike, in consequence of the unbearable tyranny to which they have been subjected.

